{"data":[{"question":"Many of the early word of T.S Eliot expresses the anguish and barrenness of modern life and the isolation of the individual.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The novel","b":"reveal","c":"joy of black life","d":"rural Georgia","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Reveal-> reveals","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The novel reveal the horror, drudgery, and joy of black life in rural Georgia.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"During","b":"ceremonies","c":"guests","d":"silence","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Silence-> silent","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"During wedding ceremonies in the United States, guests are usually silence.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"How","b":"in the shadow","c":"the","d":"an","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- How-> when","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"How the Earth is in the shadow of the moon, we see an eclipse of the sun.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The children's","b":"called","c":"seeing","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Seeing-> seen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The children's television program called Sesame Street was seeing in 84 countries in 1989.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"research","b":"what","c":"link between","d":"and","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- What-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Some research suggests what there is a link between the body's calcium balance and tooth decay.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"her","b":"into","c":"of","d":"in a book","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- In a book-> in the book","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Louisa May Alcott infused her own life into the character of Jo in a book Little Women.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Rock music","b":"original","c":"country music","d":"and","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Original-> originated from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Rock music was original a mixture of country music and rhythm and blues.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"increasing","b":"of","c":"works","d":"daily","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Works-> workers","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Traveling ballet companies were uncommon before her Augusta Maywood formed the first traveling troupe.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Traveling","b":"were","c":"her","d":"traveling","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n-Her->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The virtues of ordinary life is the focus of many poems.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"ordinary","c":"is","d":"many","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Is -> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}